yo yo yo you're all on periscope
welcome to periscope come a holiday
party where we have merchandise store as
you can see here to buy cries this is
the self-driving car awareness week to
check out the EON playing music if you
would like your very own eon just go
right now
the shop.com yeah you don't even have to
be here there's a verbal agreement why
do I just remove ease
[Music]
$6.99 can be yours let me tell you when
they're shipping even if you buy them
today any working hard it's not
Christmas all the common team will sign
it yes no that's not the Macintosh I'm
not Steve Jobs you know all Macintosh's
inside Macintosh case it was signed that
every member
[Music]
somebody is very angry that you guys are
not going to New York our awareness to
our team is pressed not from San
Francisco not from technology and not
from automotive we're looking for local
press in Midwest states politician local
presses like chill you know what I'm
gonna call those guys still be chill
press somewhere that isn't crazy
Journal you have a radio host in
Minnesota if you want me to channel
somebody requested a freestyle from
George
I'll be making my money and smoking my
weed that's why she texts me and tell me
she loved me she know that one day
because I got it coming those are the
teaser George TT I mean no come on does
Cersei no no no no no be serious
rhetoric isn't real please feel God be
real look let me tell you about Silicon
Valley you guys this place is full of
these people are already
destroyed but you know some people are
trying to fight back anyone out there
come and visit online
[Music]
Omaha we've got lots of people out there
being aggressive
someone just say coke boys like like
cocaine like pain or like brothers
there's honestly no cojes party okay so
I go on this baby
Rufus yeah what is that if that comments
a lot though so what you said something
I heard we do yeah some oh okay okay
they're just by seed of the I don't even
I don't even know that I all I can do
all I can do is move your back up to
sixteen talking to me that's why we said
when you're talking to me because we
only get one conversation a week can I
get one conversation at least shout out
to everyone making my beats you helping
me preach the music's the only thing
keeping the peace when I'm falling to
pieces
[Music]
we need yours so we could try to play
Benny's chop but no because we respect
Spotify terms of circles and a deal all
right we got more people here I'm going
to go thanks for watching thanks for
joining us my periscope